Like all things on this hurtling sphere...
...I emerged from the molten center
of creation.
But mine has been a unique path.
Isolated, I developed attributes
beyond those of lesser beings.
Then the sphere was struck
by a vast celestial stone.
Black chunks of death filled the skies...
...and the world
became a chaotic garden of doom.
Soon the sphere began
to nurture new kinds of life.
And there was one
that stood above all the rest.
Its fragile shell belied its vicious nature.
And in what seemed like a heartbeat...
...these things proliferated in both number
and destructive means.
Now they have harnessed
the most destructive force.
And I, The Centre, have concluded...
...that the sphere
must be cleansed of them.
This is Lois Lane on Armed Forces Radio.
Well, boys, it looks like the party's over.
They signed the ceasefire.
So have a drink and smoke them
if you got them.
We're going home.
Some way to end a war, huh, kid?
Nobody wins, nobody loses.
Long as it's over, Ace. I got plans.
Right, I forgot.
You're gonna be a space ranger.
The proper term is "test pilot,"
funny man.
I'm gonna see the stars, close up.
Hey.
Sons of bitches must not have heard
about the ceasefire.
I'm coming back for you.
Try using your guns for a change.
Can you make it back now, Ace?
Roger that.
Gotta get me a new pair of skivvies.
Got another bogey.
Hal, your engine.
Punch out. Punch out!
Listen to me. War over.
Finished.
It's over.
War over.
I'm so sorry.
All I wanted was to send a signal
to Mars.
How could I have known
it would teleport you here?
I suppose we both got the shock
of our lives.
But your heart must be stronger
than mine.
Whoever you are...
...forgive me.
Come on in, Kal.
Join the celebration.
Diana, what's going on here?
Tell them they'd be wasting their bullets.
Don't judge them, KaI.
They get a little nervous around men now.
What are you talking about?
-I was heading upriver...
...when I passed this village
about four days ago.
The people here helped the French.
The rebels didn't like that.
They murdered the men and children
and they threw them in the river.
These women were beaten and penned
in tiger cages for the rebels to use.
The rebels, how did they die?
I only disarmed them.
I left their guns in a clearing and
then I let the women out of their cages.
They did this?
And you just stood by and watched?
I gave them freedom
and a chance for justice.
You know, the American way.
This is what the government's afraid of,
Diana.
Us acting like vigilantes.
I have to do what I think is right.
That's what the others said at first,
remember?
And now Batman's a fugitive,
the whole Justice Society's retired...
...and Hourman's dead.
No matter how much good we do...
...deep down, people are always
going to be scared of us.
Isn't that why you and I
signed those loyalty oaths?
Take a look around, Kal.
Oaths don't mean much here.
All I see is suffering and madness.
But...
-There's the door, spaceman.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The downed pilot insisted
the island was teeming with dinosaurs...
...but Navy sources claim
a search revealed...
...that not only were there no dinosaurs,
there wasn't even an island.
In other news-
Well, I don't know, Groucho,
that's not really what I meant.
We keep our farm animals in the farm,
not in the house.
Not in the bedroom, certainly.
Eh, what's up, doc?
This now concludes our broadcasting day.
The last I heard,
she went back to Paradise Island.
It sounds like she's lost her mind.
I don't think it's that simple.
Diana's an Amazon
who's become an American.
She's trying to make sense
of her convictions.
Between her and that Batman character...
I thought these people were your friends.
-They are.
But neither of them would sacrifice
their principles for a friend.
Ever since McCarthy came to-
-McCarthy. He's no excuse.
Whatever party, whatever administration,
there'll always be boogeymen like him.
We need our heroes to stand up...
...and show us what this country
is supposed to mean.
We need a leader.
Come on, rolI it.
Come on, eight. Come on, eight.
Yes.
Ten's the number to win.
Now why don't you tell me
what we're doing here, Ace?
Told you, HaI, it's a surprise.
You'll find out tomorrow.
Now, roll those dice before they cool off.
Come on, 10.
Ten. It's a winner.
And you have the loveliest light
in your eyes, dig?
Can we get back to the interview, please?
-Oh, yeah. My philosophy of life.
Tell your readers they gotta do what I do,
live for the moment...
...because it might be our last,
you dig, Miss West?
Very profound.
-That's me.
I've always been, you know,
deep like that.
Time for the sound check, boss.
Back in a moment.
I'll try to live for it.
I tell you, these two heavyweights
are giving us quite a show tonight.
Oh, it looks like it'Il have to wait
for the next round, folks.
Meantime, we've got the champ...
...Ted "Wildcat" Grant,
solidly ahead on points.
Uh, hello.
-Hello, Barry?
Iris. I thought you had to work tonight.
I do.
But I wanted to tell you
how much I miss you.
You have no idea.
-Come on, how could you miss me?
You're in Las Vegas interviewing
all those singers and movie stars.
It's the fast lane.
There are lots of potholes
in that lane, let me tell you.
Iris? Iris.
Sorry to interrupt your festivities,
but if you all stay calm...
...we'll be gone as soon as my friends here
come back from the cashiers' booths.
The key phrase was "stay calm. "
Iris, what's happening?
You there.
The naughty girl on the phone.
Iris!
Just a few more seconds, everyone.
Ah, my ride is here.
Wait.
Make it quick.
Hot damn, Ace.
It's that super-fast guy from CentraI City.
The Flash. He'll take care of this clown.
I took precautions
in case you dropped by.
If you so much as touch me...
...you'Il trigger six cryogenic bombs
I've hidden around the city.
And they'll go off in 90 seconds anyway,
unless you find them.
So it's your choice now.
Me, or the city and everyone in it.
Eighty-nine, 88-
One...
...two, three, four...
...five. Where's six?
It took me a second or two,
but I figured out the sixth bomb...
...was just a wild-goose chase.
You are different
from the other lesser beings. Faster.
Why?
-Lesser beings?
What are you talking about?
Eh? Wha-?
What did you do?
I rewired it on the way down.
Don't ever mess with my Iris.
This little trip's been fun.
Are you ever gonna tell me
where we're headed?
To hell if you don't slow down.
What's wrong with you?
Ever since you got out of the hospitaI...
It was Korea.
Changed everything.
Wars have a tendency to do that.
Look, Ace, you know
that ever since I was a kid...
...watching my old man fly,
I wanted to see the stars.
But the war and then the hospital...
...it's like I'm damaged goods.
I can't get a first-class outfit
to take me on. And without a ride...
...I sure can't climb the pyramid.
Slow down.
-Why bother?
You have to, kid, because we're here.
It's where you get your second chance.
How did you know he was the commie?
He came back for the formula,
that's what nailed it.
He could've killed you.
Like I always say,
when you know you're right...
...it's worth taking a chance.
Now, come here.
Ace Morgan's recommendation
carries a lot of weight at Ferris Aircraft.
I assume he spoke as well of us to you.
He did. And I can't imagine anywhere else
I'd rather be right now, Miss Ferris.
Do you have any questions?
I'm surprised your father
isn't interviewing me.
Not that I mind, it's just that you're a-
-A woman?
My father trusts me with the day-to-day
operation of the company.
If that's good enough for him, it ought to-
-Whoa, wait.
I was only saying that you're a little young
to be running a major corporation.
Oh. Oh, you're good, flyboy...
...but save it for the girls
in the typing pool.
One last question.
In your resume, there's a gap
between July and December of '53.
I was in a VA hospitaI.
Psych ward.
Most people wouldn't talk about
this kind of thing...
...but I learned a lot about myself there.
I came out knowing who I really am
and what I really want.
You report for training
and security clearance in two weeks.
All right, let's celebrate.
Waiter, some champagne.
Look, HaI,
I don't get involved with my employees.
I understand, Carol...
...but I don't start work
for two more weeks.
Two glasses.
So where'd this hot tip come from, John?
-A source.
WelI, I think I know your secret.
You do?
-Hm.
The tips you get from out of the blue...
...those hunches of yours
that always turn out to be right.
You're dating a fortuneteller.
No, I-
Something like that.
Try the back.
I'll see if I can pick this lock.
You are the tribute.
Yours is the glory
of nourishing the strength...
...of The Centre.
You okay, John?
No, stay away.
Stay away!
Back off, you're scaring the boy.
You'll be alI right now that-
You wilI be judged too.
You wilI all be judged.
Without The Centre, there is no holding.
The Centre? What's The Centre?
Jordan, do you copy?
Negative, Colonel Flagg, no Jordan here...
-... just Spam in a can.
Cut the comedy.
Are you go for 72?
Yes, Captain Personality.
Jordan is go for exercise 72.
Hit it.
-My pleasure.
Spam Jordan is now go for exercise 73.
How's he doing?
-He's tough enough, that's for sure.
But I'm getting sick of his attitude.
-He's a pilot, ColoneI Flagg.
He's used to making decisions
and being in control.
This training goes against his nature.
Can't be helped.
It's all part of the big picture.
Which he hasn't seen yet.
CaroI.
I mean, Miss Ferris, afternoon.
Afternoon, Mr. Jordan.
I trust ColoneI Flagg is keeping you busy.
This stuff? Child's play, Miss Ferris.
Perhaps later I could show you-
Jordan.
What?
-Exercise 73, remember?
Yeah, they tell me 73's the charm.
Good day, Miss Ferris.
What are his numbers, Harry?
-Uh...
Excellent.
Responses in the 99th percentile.
Hm.
Not that I'm complaining,
but where exactly are you taking me?
Where have you always wanted to go?
-That's a leading question.
No, I mean, since you were a kid.
Your big goal?
-The stars.
But at the rate we're going, the Russians
are gonna beat us into orbit by months.
Who said anything about orbit?
Whoa!
A hole in the ground.
Isn't that the wrong direction?
Sometimes you have to go through hell
to get to heaven.
What is all this?
Welcome to the reaI Ferris Aircraft.
See that sour-looking man down there?
He'Il explain everything.
His name's Faraday.
Works for the government.
And if you like Rick Flagg,
you'll love him.
You're weak, erratic, emotional...
...and for my money, at least a little pink.
But I'm told you're the best we've got.
I...
-You keep your mouth shut...
...and your ears open.
I'm about to share some of this nation's
greatest secrets with you.
Couple of years ago, we found the body
of a radical scientist named Erdel...
...in a small observatory near Gotham.
Somehow,
he'd been able to contact Mars.
Mars? You're joking, right?
Yes, Jordan, I'm a real kidder.
We found this footprint
at the observatory.
Did you find what made that print?
No.
Whatever it is,
it's eluded us for two years.
There's life on Mars, Jordan.
And it's come to Earth.
Look, I'm just a pilot.
What does this have to do with me?
You haven't figured it out yet?
We've got to know what these Martians
want from us...
...and since we can't find them
here on Earth...
...we're going to Mars.
Outstanding.
Welcome home, Mr. Jones.
Why didn't I-?
Why didn't you sense me as you do others?
That's my secret.
Why are you here?
Because of The Centre?
The cult's spreading all over the world.
At first I thought it might be
the communists.
But they're having trouble
with the cults too.
It's not ideologicaI.
There's some kind
of psychic force involved.
It's affecting people
with high susceptibility.
Getting into their minds.
I felt it.
Yes, your feelings. How-?
Let's just say that's my secret.
You came here because
you want to work together, true?
True.
-Then we'll share our information.
I've already collected some.
Newspaper clippings.
You'll have to do better than that.
And one other thing, I'm not sure
what you are or where you come from...
...but my instincts tell me
you're to be trusted.
Make no mistake, though.
I have a $70,000 sliver
of radioactive meteor...
...to stop the one from Metropolis.
With you, all I need is a penny
for a book of matches.
What's the matter, Grodd,
feeling starved for attention?
You're government property now, swifty.
We're gonna find out
what makes you tick.
Hey.
Did you see that?
Where did he go?
What you got there, John?
A kids' book?
-Not exactly.
The author committed suicide
a while back.
He thought the world was about to end.
You like this weird stuff, don't you?
WelI, you should see what they got
in the interrogation room.
He shot a cop on the parkway.
Then we found his mother...
...in his trunk.
Mental case?
-Not your typical one.
This guy's a scientist.
You're here to kill me, aren't you?
You're part of it.
I'm not going to kill you.
And what do you think I'm part of?
The Centre. It's everywhere.
What do you know about The Centre?
It's gonna kill everyone.
I was trying to get away from it.
How do you know alI this?
I just do. I can feel it.
I tried to get in on the Mars mission
but they wouldn't take me.
The Mars mission?
Yes. They're going to Mars.
It's safe there.
Who is going to Mars?
-The government.
They won't let us normaI people go.
Normal people.
Hello, Harry.
I've been very worried about you.
No! Don't let him near me.
Special Agent Faraday.
Harry used to be a helI of a scientist.
Did lots of classified stuff.
We can't leave him in a regular institution
because of what he might spilI.
You're referring to the Mars mission?
The what?
-He told me about a mission to Mars.
He's even farther gone than I thought.
If that's possible.
Now, come on, Harry.
-No, please don't let him take me.
Please, please.
Mr. Faraday, if there's anything else
I can do for you, please let me know.
Sure.
We've been able to contact Mars.
Life on Mars.
We're going to Mars.
See you around, Jones.
It's all true.
Wilson's vigilante activities...
...kept the local white supremacists
at bay for years...
...but his luck ran out yesterday
when he was caught by a mob and killed.
Police say they have no suspects.
In other news- Hey.
Sorry to interrupt. There's something
I have to get off my chest.
I've always used my power
to help people...
...but the government's on my tail,
hunting me like a criminal.
You just saw what happened
to John Wilson.
America needs more people like him.
But where are they going to come from
if our government keeps acting this way?
As for me, I'm quitting, giving it up.
Breaks my heart but there are people I love.
I don't want anything to happen to them.
So good night, everybody, and good luck.
Who needed him anyway?
-Probably some kind of crook.
Definitely a freak.
-Definitely.
And what was with that red costume?
Red's for commies.
Hey, where are you going?
-Home.
Mr. Jones...
...how did you locate me?
I may not be the world's greatest
detective, but I have my methods.
This is alI the information
I've been able to collect.
It's the last of it.
I thought I could make a life for myself
here among you humans.
I didn't think I had a choice.
But there is one now.
There's just too much hatred here,
too much ignorance...
...too much mindless conformity.
I'm leaving.
Have a nice trip.
Some of us don't have that luxury.
Flying Cloud, status report.
Flying Cloud is go. Secure for launch.
Jordan?
-Go.
Good luck, Flying Cloud.
God be with you.
Go for launch on alI points.
Roger, we are go for launch.
Ignition sequence start.
Primary engines engaged.
All engines running.
Don't move, Martian.
Ten, nine, eight, seven...
...six, five...
...four, three, two, one.
Almost there.
We're losing pressure.
We're gonna have to take her back.
-Too risky.
Jordan, listen to me.
We have weapons on board.
-What?
In case the Martians
turned out to be hostile.
Nerve gas, germ bombs, even nuclear.
Doesn't make a difference.
I can stilI land this thing.
What's that?
-It's a destruct switch.
I'm sorry, Jordan,
but you knew the risks.
You just relax, colonel.
I'll have you on the ground in no time.
What's going on there?
Come in, Flying Cloud.
We've had an engine failure.
I'm gonna glide her back.
Negative, it's too dangerous.
Where's Flagg?
-Don't worry about him...
...or your weapons. They'll both be okay.
Weapons?
You son of a bitch.
Jordan, put Flagg back on.
No can do, Faraday. He's indisposed.
Call in the big guy.
Flagg, don't. I can land it.
I can't bet the world on that, Jordan.
Nuclear weapons?
Nerve gas? What were you thinking?
We didn't know. We're still not sure.
Of what, exactly?
If we can trust him.
You trust me and I'm an alien.
-Yeah, but...
It's because he looks
so different, isn't it?
You have to admit-
-Listen, you've seen the power he has.
He could leave this place
any time he wants.
But he hasn't.
That should telI you something.
Tell me about this America, Diana.
It's changed since the war.
Back then, we were in the right.
It was simple.
They still say they're in the right
but they don't act that way.
Men.
Things have changed here too, Diana.
A lot of us are beginning to think we need
a leader who sticks closer to home.
And who would such a leader be?
You?
You might need a little more seasoning.
Hal Jordan.
You know me?
Who are you?
I am...
...Abin Sur.
You need a doctor. Let me-
Listen to me.
What I have to telI you
will seem unbelievable but-
I am the Green Lantern of Sector 2814.
I was on my way here to help.
Help? How?
In the coming battle with The Centre.
Center of what?
It is a monstrous creature
that fears you humans so much...
...it intends to eradicate every
living souI on the planet.
When I was entering your atmosphere
a few days ago...
...there was a huge explosion.
There was too much yellow energy
for me.
I ordered my ring to find you.
I had to find a deserving one.
A man entirely without fear.
A lot of people think I'm a coward
because of what happened in the war.
Did your ring telI you about that?
You are no coward, Hal Jordan.
To you, all life is precious.
And this ring is far too powerful
to fall into the hands of someone...
...who doesn't understand that.
How does this thing work?
The Guardians...
They will...
Wow, you really do know him.
And you must be Robin.
I hear you're quite a detective.
WelI, I try not to brag, but-
Have you finished your homework yet?
Uh... Right.
Hm. New look, a sidekick.
Do you mind if I ask-?
-As a matter of fact, I do.
Let's just say I set out to scare criminals,
not children.
Fair enough.
This alI lines up with dozens of stories
we've run in the Planet this year.
The children's book
is particularly ominous.
As if someone, something else...
...were speaking through the author.
-in its wake. We have a live report
coming in from Cape Canaveral.
The creature is hovering over
the large fuel tanks here at the Cape...
...making it impossible for the Army
to use their missiles on it.
Lois.
-Its wingspan is easily the length...
...of a football field...
...and it looks a lot like
a prehistoric pterodactyl.
But much, much bigger.
I'm not sure of what it's trying to do.
Diana.
Haven't flown this thing in years.
Guess I'm a little rusty.
Easy, easy.
We fought it, hard as we could, but-
It's coming, KaI.
It's coming here.
Medic!
We know this place could
never hold someone with your powers.
Why do you stay?
-I'm determined to beat you at this game.
Without reading your mind.
Come on, level with me.
Very well.
I have looked into your mind,
and by extension, your heart.
You honestly believe
that there wilI be a better day...
...when all of this won't be necessary.
To find that within you, Mr. Faraday,
has filled my heart with hope.
And I have no place else to go.
This just came in from Washington,
urgent.
It's The Centre, isn't it?
I can feeI its presence very strongly now.
You're looking for a place to go?
I got one helI of a destination for you.
But we might not come back.
I'm ready.
The last time I appeared
without warning in this form...
...someone died of fright.
Perhaps I should take a friendlier
appearance.
Suit yourself.
WelI?
It's okay. But real men wear pants.
-this absolutely unprecedented
situation off the coast of Florida.
The combined might
of the U.S. Armed Forces...
...had no effect on this-
-Bourbon, please.
I hardly know what to call it.
It appears we've reestablished contact
with our reporter at the scene.
The only word I can find
to describe the scale of this is "biblical. "
It's a living island,
at least 25 miles across.
It has large ports which
discharge intense blasts of energy...
...but which can also draw things
into the creature.
Not two minutes ago, we watched it inhale
an entire aircraft carrier.
The loss of life out here
is incalculable and-
Wait. We're turning around.
We've been ordered back.
I have to tell you something.
I'm the F...
-I already know.
You what?
I'm a reporter, remember?
I always suspected, and I heard your voice
on the news the other night.
I was only trying to protect you.
They think I'm some kind of criminal.
But we know better, don't we?
So, what are you waiting for?
You know who's going to be there?
Superman, Wonder Woman, people like that.
I'm just a guy who runs
after jewelry thieves and talking gorillas.
You're more than that.
And you're going to prove it.
What are you doing?
Where have you been?
And what happened to the simulator?
Long story.
Have you seen the news?
Do you have any idea what's-
Oh, God.
You're going down there, aren't you?
Hal the pacifist is going down there
to get killed by that thing.
What would you have me do?
Or do you think I'm a coward too?
I looked up your war record.
You never fired
at those North Korean planes.
Maybe I just didn't believe that what
we were doing there was worth killing for.
But in that trench,
I found out what would make me kill.
Survival. I would kill to survive.
Aren't you going to at least say goodbye?
Don't you-?
Whoa. We're just here to help.
We don't need help.
Especially not from you.
You think you can hit me?
It's been tried before.
Don't push us, mister.
I see I have your attention.
We face a threat big enough
to wipe us off the Earth...
...and still we bicker about a mask
or a uniform.
My best friend is lying upstairs right now.
She would have given her life
for this country...
...and I could hardly look her in the eye.
America was founded on the notion...
...that a person should be free
to follow his or her destiny.
But we can't do that if we're living in fear
of our own government.
We need to reclaim this country
for free men and women everywhere.
What about your government friends?
-That's a fair question.
Superman's right.
The persecution and paranoia
have to stop.
From here on,
we work together as free Americans.
I'm gonna fly out now
and recon this thing.
When I get back,
we'Il work out a strategy.
Are you with me?
America's champion, Superman...
...went down in defeat severaI hours ago.
An exhaustive search
has found no sign of him.
Here at the Cape,
the greatest minds in the free world...
...are now working on a plan to stop
this monster...
...before it reaches the coast.
We cannot panic.
We cannot let our sense of loss-
If this book's right...
...it's a whole new life form
we've never even imagined.
Or it could be nothing more than
the ravings of some demented cartoonist.
It's not. I assure you.
And there's only one way
to stop this thing now.
I want you all to listen to this man.
Gentlemen, I'm Ray Palmer
from Ivy University.
I've heard of you, Palmer,
and your invention.
Matter reduction, right?
Right. I...
-It won't work.
Everything it shrinks becomes unstable.
Exactly.
We start with an all-out aeriaI assault.
We hit the thing from every direction
at once. That's a distraction.
While it's fighting the Air Corps,
we use this baby on it.
This gizmo uses light to shrink things.
Question...
-Wait.
Everything the ray shrinks
becomes unstable.
Meaning, it explodes.
Still have a question?
That thing out there is one
hell of a lot bigger than an orange.
How are you gonna?
-It is big.
And that's why we have to expose
its surface to the ray piece by piece.
All in the blink of an eye?
That's impossible without Superman.
No, it's not impossible, is it?
Piece of cake.
Any other questions?
Just one.
-Jordan.
About time.
-Attacking the surface won't be enough...
...to distract this thing.
You need someone
to go inside with bombs.
You volunteering?
-He'd better...
...because I'm not going in there alone.
Outstanding.
All of you, remember...
...today there are no Democrats,
no Republicans.
No hawks, no doves.
Just the naked simplicity of an absolute:
Mankind's survival.
Good luck to us all.
All right, men.
Our job is to protect Flash until Morgan
and Jordan light it up.
I want...
-Hey, look out!
Hawk! Ah!
Are you all right?
-It's attacking my mind.
All of you, fight on!
To the last breath, fight on!
All weapons systems hot.
Like they say, it ain't when you go,
it's how you go.
Uh, Hal?
What's wrong?
Whatever you see, ignore it.
Just keep going. Acknowledge.
Just keep going. No problem.
What now?
This stuff is no hallucination,
-I'll tell you that.
And whatever it is,
I think it's trying to get inside.
Drop the bombs,
then we'll burn our way out.
Roger that.
My rockets are dead.
Can't open bomb bay doors.
Hal?
-I'm here.
We've had our ride
and it's time to punch our ticket.
Initiate manual detonation.
Roger.
Hal Jordan, you are the key.
Your will drives the ring.
Clear your mind
and focus on what matters.
Hal? What-?
Later.
You're afraid.
It's all on me.
The whole thing.
We'll be there for you.
We all will.
Godspeed.
He did it. Son of a bitch.
I was afraid...
...I'd be late for the victory party.
Spoke too soon.
That thing's gonna do a lot of damage.
Guess it's time to see what this ring can do.
Hey.
Sorry.
That guy with the ring,
he wasn't part of the plan.
Or wasn't I listening?
You won't be able to do it.
It is The Centre that holds, not you.
I can. I can.
You do not have the will.
No?
Watch.
Whoo-hoo!
Hey, Ace, what happened
to that buddy of yours?
Hal Jordan?
If I know him, he's up there somewhere
tear-assing around.
I am Arthur of Atlantis.
This one has been asking
for a woman named Lois.
The pioneers gave up their safety,
their comfort...
...and sometimes their lives
to build our new West.
They were determined
to make the new world strong and free...
...an example to the world.
Some would say that those struggles
are all over.
That all the horizons have been explored.
That all the battles have been won.
That there is no longer
an American frontier.
And we stand today on the edge
of a new frontier.
The frontier of unknown opportunities
and perils.
Beyond that frontier are uncharted areas
of science and space.
Unsolved problems of peace and war.
Unconquered pockets
of ignorance and prejudice.
I'm asking each of you...
...to be pioneers
towards that new frontier.
My call is to the young at heart,
regardless of age.
Can we carry through in an age...
...where we will witness not only new
breakthroughs in weapons of destruction...
...but also a race for mastery
of the sky and the rain...
...the ocean and the tides,
the far side of space...
...and the inside of men's minds?
All mankind waits upon our decision.
A whole world looks to see
what we shall do.
And we cannot fail their trust.
And we cannot fail to try.